<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="app_name">Movies App</string>
    <string name="menu_movies">Movies</string>
    <string name="menu_tvshow">TV Show</string>

    <string name="text_logo_navDraw">movies app</string>
    <string name="action_language">Languages</string>


    <string-array name="data_name_movies">
        <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bird Box</item>
        <item>Bumblebee</item>
        <item>Once Upon a Deadpool</item>
        <item>DragonBall Super: Broly</item>
        <item>Robin Hood</item>
        <item>Spiderman : Into the Spider-Verse</item>
        <item>Venom</item>

        <item>Sonic the Hedgehog</item>
        <item>Ad Astra</item>
        <item>1917</item>
        <item>Bloodshot</item>
        <item>13 Hours: The Secret Soldiers of Benghazi</item>
        <item>El Camino: A Breaking Bad Movie</item>
        <item>Parasite</item>
        <item>Escape from Pretoria</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_date_movies">
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>
        <item>2018</item>

        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2020</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_score_movies">
        <item>80%</item>
        <item>68%</item>
        <item>83%</item>
        <item>69%</item>
        <item>65%</item>
        <item>69%</item>
        <item>74%</item>
        <item>58%</item>
        <item>84%</item>
        <item>66%</item>

        <item>73%</item>
        <item>60%</item>
        <item>80%</item>
        <item>61%</item>
        <item>71%</item>
        <item>69%</item>
        <item>86%</item>
        <item>72%</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_genre_movies">
        <item>Music, Biography, Drama</item>
        <item>Action, Adventure, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Sci-fi, Adventure, Action</item>
        <item>Thriller, Drama</item>
        <item>Sci-fi, Adventure, Action</item>
        <item>Comedy, Action</item>
        <item>Action, Animation</item>
        <item>Thriller, Adventure, Action</item>
        <item>Action, Comedy, Sci-fi</item>
        <item>Sci-fi, Action</item>

        <item>Action, Sci-fi, Comedy</item>
        <item>Sci-fi, Drama, Thriller</item>
        <item>War, Drama, Action</item>
        <item>Action, Drama, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Action, History, Thriller</item>
        <item>Crime, Drama, Thriller</item>
        <item>Comedy, Thriller, Drama</item>
        <item>Thriller</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_dec_movies">
        <item>  Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</item>
        <item>  Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
        <item>  As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>  Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
        <item>  On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</item>
        <item>  A kidnapped Fred Savage is forced to endure Deadpool\'s PG-13 rendition of Deadpool 2 as a Princess Bride-esque story that\'s full of magic, wonder &amp; zero F\'s.</item>
        <item>  Earth is peaceful following the Tournament of Power. Realizing that the universes still hold many more strong people yet to see, Goku spends all his days training to reach even greater heights. Then one day, Goku and Vegeta are faced by a Saiyan called \'Broly\' who they\'ve never seen before. The Saiyans were supposed to have been almost completely wiped out in the destruction of Planet Vegeta, so what\'s this one doing on Earth? This encounter between the three Saiyans who have followed completely different destinies turns into a stupendous battle, with even Frieza (back from Hell) getting caught up in the mix.</item>
        <item>  A war-hardened Crusader and his Moorish commander mount an audacious revolt against the corrupt English crown.</item>
        <item>  Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a spider-man. When Wilson \"Kingpin\" Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.</item>
        <item>  Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.</item>

        <item>Based on the global blockbuster videogame franchise from Sega, Sonic the Hedgehog tells the story of the world’s speediest hedgehog as he embraces his new home on Earth. In this live-action adventure comedy, Sonic and his new best friend team up to defend the planet from the evil genius Dr. Robotnik and his plans for world domination. Featured Crew</item>
        <item>The near future, a time when both hope and hardships drive humanity to look to the stars and beyond. While a mysterious phenomenon menaces to destroy life on planet Earth, astronaut Roy McBride undertakes a mission across the immensity of space and its many perils to uncover the truth about a lost expedition that decades before boldly faced emptiness and silence in search of the unknown.</item>
        <item>At the height of the First World War, two young British soldiers must cross enemy territory and deliver a message that will stop a deadly attack on hundreds of soldiers.</item>
        <item>After he and his wife are murdered, marine Ray Garrison is resurrected by a team of scientists. Enhanced with nanotechnology, he becomes a superhuman, biotech killing machine - Bloodshot. As Ray first trains with fellow super-soldiers, he cannot recall anything from his former life. But when his memories flood back and he remembers the man that killed both him and his wife, he breaks out of the facility to get revenge, only to discover that there\'s more to the conspiracy than he thought.</item>
        <item>An American Ambassador is killed during an attack at a U.S. compound in Libya as a security team struggles to make sense out of the chaos.</item>
        <item>In the wake of his dramatic escape from captivity, Jesse Pinkman must come to terms with his past in order to forge some kind of future.</item>
        <item>All unemployed, Ki-taek\'s family takes peculiar interest in the wealthy and glamorous Parks for their livelihood until they get entangled in an unexpected incident.</item>
        <item>Two white South Africans, imprisoned for working on behalf of the ANC, are determined to escape from Pretoria\'s notorious white man\'s \'Robben Island\' Prison.</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_photo_movies">
        <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_robinhood</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>

        <item>@drawable/poster_sonic</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_adastra</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_1917</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bloodshot</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_secretbenghazi</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_elcamino</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_parasite</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_escape</item>
    </integer-array>


    <string-array name="data_name_tvshow">
        <item>The Simpsons</item>
        <item>Rick and Morty</item>
        <item>The Walking Dead</item>
        <item>Riverdale</item>
        <item>Supergirl</item>
        <item>Family Guy</item>
        <item>The Flash</item>
        <item>Star Wars: The Clone Wars</item>
        <item>Grey\'s Anatomy</item>
        <item>Star Trek: Picard</item>
        <item>Amazing Stories</item>
        <item>The Blacklist</item>

        <item>The Mandalorian</item>
        <item>Stranger Things</item>
        <item>Prison Break</item>
        <item>Outlander</item>
        <item>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</item>
        <item>Game of Thrones</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_date_tvshow">
        <item>1989</item>
        <item>2013</item>
        <item>2010</item>
        <item>2017</item>
        <item>2015</item>
        <item>1999</item>
        <item>2014</item>
        <item>2008</item>
        <item>2005</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2020</item>
        <item>2013</item>

        <item>2019</item>
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2005</item>
        <item>2015</item>
        <item>2013</item>
        <item>2011</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_score_tvshow">
        <item>72%</item>
        <item>86%</item>
        <item>73%</item>
        <item>76$</item>
        <item>63%</item>
        <item>66%</item>
        <item>69%</item>
        <item>79%</item>
        <item>67%</item>
        <item>74%</item>
        <item>78%</item>
        <item>70%</item>

        <item>82%</item>
        <item>83%</item>
        <item>76%</item>
        <item>74%</item>
        <item>78%</item>
        <item>82%</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_genre_tvshow">
        <item>Satire, Neighbor, Parody</item>
        <item>Time travel, Scientist, Alien</item>
        <item>Zombie, Survival, Horror</item>
        <item>Drama, Mystery</item>
        <item>Action, Adventure, Sci-fi</item>
        <item>High School, Satire, Parody</item>
        <item>Superhero, Super Power, DC Comics</item>
        <item>Animation, Adventure, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Doctor, Trauma, Medical Drama</item>
        <item>Sci-fi, Action</item>
        <item>Action, Adventure, Sci-fi</item>
        <item>Drama, Crime, Mystery</item>

        <item>Sci-fi, Adventure, Action</item>
        <item>Mystery, Drama, Fantasy</item>
        <item>Action, Crime, Drama</item>
        <item>Adventure, Drama, Romance</item>
        <item>Comedy, Crime</item>
        <item>Sci-fi, Drama</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_dec_tvshow">
        <item>Set in Springfield, the average American town, the show focuses on the antics and everyday adventures of the Simpson family; Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie, as well as a virtual cast of thousands. Since the beginning, the series has been a pop culture icon, attracting hundreds of celebrities to guest star. The show has also made name for itself in its fearless satirical take on politics, media and American life in general.</item>
        <item>Rick is a mentally-unbalanced but scientifically-gifted old man who has recently reconnected with his family. He spends most of his time involving his young grandson Morty in dangerous, outlandish adventures throughout space and alternate universes. Compounded with Morty\'s already unstable family life, these events cause Morty much distress at home and school.</item>
        <item>Sheriff\'s deputy Rick Grimes awakens from a coma to find a post-apocalyptic world dominated by flesh-eating zombies. He sets out to find his family and encounters many other survivors along the way.</item>
        <item>Set in the present, the series offers a bold, subversive take on Archie, Betty, Veronica and their friends, exploring the surreality of small-town life, the darkness and weirdness bubbling beneath Riverdale\’s wholesome facade.</item>
        <item>Twenty-four-year-old Kara Zor-El, who was taken in by the Danvers family when she was 13 after being sent away from Krypton, must learn to embrace her powers after previously hiding them. The Danvers teach her to be careful with her powers, until she has to reveal them during an unexpected disaster, setting her on her journey of heroism.</item>
        <item>Sick, twisted, politically incorrect and Freakin\' Sweet animated series featuring the adventures of the dysfunctional Griffin family. Bumbling Peter and long-suffering Lois have three kids. Stewie (a brilliant but sadistic baby bent on killing his mother and taking over the world), Meg (the oldest, and is the most unpopular girl in town) and Chris (the middle kid, he\'s not very bright but has a passion for movies). The final member of the family is Brian - a talking dog and much more than a pet, he keeps Stewie in check whilst sipping Martinis and sorting through his own life issues.</item>
        <item>After a particle accelerator causes a freak storm, CSI Investigator Barry Allen is struck by lightning and falls into a coma. Months later he awakens with the power of super speed, granting him the ability to move through Central City like an unseen guardian angel. Though initially excited by his newfound powers, Barry is shocked to discover he is not the only "meta-human" who was created in the wake of the accelerator explosion — and not everyone is using their new powers for good. Barry partners with S.T.A.R. Labs and dedicates his life to protect the innocent. For now, only a few close friends and associates know that Barry is literally the fastest man alive, but it won\'t be long before the world learns what Barry Allen has become The Flash.</item>
        <item>Yoda, Obi-Wan Kenobi, Anakin Skywalker, Mace Windu and other Jedi Knights lead the Grand Army of the Republic against the droid army of the Separatists Featured Crew</item>
        <item>Follows the personal and professional lives of a group of doctors at Seattle\’s Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital.</item>
        <item>Set twenty years after the events of Star Trek Nemesis, we follow the now-retired Admiral Picard into the next chapter of his life.</item>
        <item>Each episode transports the audience to worlds of wonder through the lens of today\’s most imaginative filmmakers, directors and writers. A reimagining of the original anthology series by Steven Spielberg.</item>
        <item>Raymond "Red" Reddington, one of the FBI\'s most wanted fugitives, surrenders in person at FBI Headquarters in Washington, D.C. He claims that he and the FBI have the same interests: bringing down dangerous criminals and terrorists. In the last two decades, he\'s made a list of criminals and terrorists that matter the most but the FBI cannot find because it does not know they exist. Reddington calls this "The Blacklist". Reddington will co-operate, but insists that he will speak only to Elizabeth Keen, a rookie FBI profiler.</item>

        <item>After the fall of the Galactic Empire, lawlessness has spread throughout the galaxy. A lone gunfighter makes his way through the outer reaches, earning his keep as a bounty hunter.</item>
        <item>When a young boy vanishes, a small town uncovers a mystery involving secret experiments, terrifying supernatural forces, and one strange little girl.</item>
        <item>Due to a political conspiracy, an innocent man is sent to death row and his only hope is his brother, who makes it his mission to deliberately get himself sent to the same prison in order to break the both of them out, from the inside out.</item>
        <item>The story of Claire Randall, a married combat nurse from 1945 who is mysteriously swept back in time to 1743, where she is immediately thrown into an unknown world where her life is threatened. When she is forced to marry Jamie, a chivalrous and romantic young Scottish warrior, a passionate affair is ignited that tears Claire\'s heart between two vastly different men in two irreconcilable lives.</item>
        <item>A single-camera ensemble comedy following the lives of an eclectic group of detectives in a New York precinct, including one slacker who is forced to shape up when he gets a new boss.</item>
        <item>Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Night\'s Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and icy horrors beyond.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_photo_tvshow">
        <item>@drawable/poster_simpsons</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_rick</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_thewalkingdead</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_riverdale</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_supergirl</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_familyguy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_theflash</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_starwars</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_greyanatomy</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_startrek</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_amazing_story</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_theblacklist</item>

        <item>@drawable/poster_themandalorian</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_strangerthings</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_prisonbreak</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_outlander</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_brooklyn</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_got</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="action_detail">Take Action</string>
    <string name="btn_watchlist">Watchlist</string>
    <string name="overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="release_year">- release year</string>
    <string name="btn_add_watchlist"> added to watchlist</string>


</resources>
